# KEVIN PAUL

#### DATA SCIENCE ENGINEER

: Regency Apts 801 Sardar Patel Rd, Chennai-600113

&: +91 9962222991

## OBJECTIVE

Professional and positive work ethic-oriented Information Technology major currently attending College of Engineering, Guindy (Anna University) with 4 months of work experience. Aiming to leverage a proven knowledge of Emerging Data Science Technologies, Application Development, and Image Processing skills to successfully fill the Data Analysis integrated role at your company. Frequently praised as focused and perseverant by my peers, I can be relied upon to help your company achieve its goals.

#### EDUCATION

## College of Engineering, Guindy

July 2017- Apr 2022
Bachelor of Technology (B. Tech) in
Information Technology

 Chettinad Vidyashram June 2003 - Apr 2017
 Higher Secondary School

#### KEY SKILLS -

- Leadership
- Technical Ability
- Analytical Thinking
- Work Ethic
- Conflict Resolution

#### AWARDS

- Multiple GPA awards throughout school
- Member of the Quiz, Football teams at the school level
- Active member of the theatre community
- Multiple literary competitions awards throughout school

#### EXPERIENCE

#### • Spritle Software

Machine Learning Intern *(Oct 2020- Dec 2020)*Worked in a robust computer enhanced environment where ML dwells deep into technical and mechanical workplaces. Involved in working in real time ComputerVision integrated projects where datasets are collected, analyzed and trained to obtain meaningful algorithms to complement work rate and produce a convenient and idealistic resolution.

#### 3G Institute of Research and Policy Studies

Technical Intern (Nov 2019 - Dec 2019)

A one-month internship on the various aspects of Data Analysis and Computer Vision to be used practically with several hands-on projects done in an IoT medium using the Blynk Cloud Environment. Learnt several different applications of Neural Networking as well.

## TECHNICAL SKILL

### Programming Languages with experience in:

- Python
- C++
- Java

## Fields with Experience in:

- Data Science and Analysis
- Neural Networking
- Image Processing
- Computer Vision